Hope the water's not too cold.
This is my last chance.
Why is it when you need money the most,
it's never around?
It happens to me all the time,
but that doesn't mean
it's still not depressing.
I can't believe how strong he is.
Nothing's stronger than money.
Well, shit.
You know, that's the same look
every super has.
Like you really believe
you're something unique.
I love it.
It makes the look I see
in your corpses' eyes
so much more invigorating.
It's for you.
I said it's for you.
You must know this
better than anyone by now,
but money is power.
Don't you agree?
Who is this?
I'm the chairman of the Mundane Vanguard.
In all fights where money is concerned,
whoever has more of it will win.
I don't think I have to tell you
who that is.
How about we end the fighting
here and now?
All you have to do
is sell your power to us.
Take some time
to come up with an offer for the sale.
Whatever it is, I'll pay.
In the meantime,
let's call a temporary truce.
Since that day,
the Mundane Vanguard
has been eerily quiet.
MY MIN-SUK
Hey.
TREAT DEBTORS LIKE FAMILY
Are you almost there?
Yes. I'm pretty close now.
Remember to ask them
about the formal meeting with my parents.
Mm-hmm.
How's work?
I'm looking over their books now.
It's a total mess.
You sure about this job?
With what they're paying,
of course I'm sure about it.
Hang on.
Did something happen?
You're freaking me out.
Nah, nothing has happened.
I'll call you again later.
-Okay. Bye.
-Mm-hmm.
NO ENTRY
FORENSICS
FIRE INVESTIGATION
We'll gather all the evidence…
You there. Make sure
to check the bottom of the pond too.
-Yes, sir.
-Be careful now.
Go deeper out.
-Well, Detective?
-Sir?
Aren't you getting in?
-There you are.
-Oh, hey.
-What time is it?
-It's just before 9:00, sir.
Maybe it's time
you replaced that old watch.
And throw out a family heirloom? No way!
Then at least get it fixed.
The parts are impossible to find.
Team leader Hwang!
Come look at this!
Right there. Look.
LOAN AGREEMENT
-A loan agreement?
-Yes.
But look. There's a name written here.
Kang Sang.
That says "Sang," doesn't it? Or--
That woman from the hotel fire.
She had a husband named Kang Sang-ung.
KANG SANG
You're engaged?
-Yep.
-Oh!
This is such wonderful news!
And I was so worried
you'd end up living alone till you died!
Living alone doesn't kill you.
That darling Min-suk is such an angel!
I could just die.
Dad, how about you?
I think--
Since when does it matter what Dad thinks?
Congratulations.
That's right. My opinion is worthless.
Ah, so then we should get dinner,
make introductions.
Oh, sure!
We're flexible, honey. You know us.
Just tell her parents to pick a date,
and we're there.
You think maybe we're rushing into things?
Oh, put a sock in it already!
All right. I'll find a day that works,
and I'll let you know.
Oh, I've never been so excited!
I'll go get the rice started.
You're staying for dinner, aren't you?
-Okay.
-Good.
You need to fill me in.
Easy.
What is it?
Is there something I forgot to tell you?
I can make cash selling.
What do you mean?
The powers I inherited.
The Mundane Vanguard.
I have a chance to sell my powers.
-Sell 'em?
-Yeah.
How would you do that?
Huh?
Do you know how it works?
How much did they offer?
They said they'd give me
whatever I wanted.
Well, these powers aren't
all that great, I suppose.
Anyway,
what will you do?
I don't know. Jeez.
Keep in mind,
they're dangerous people.
If you're not careful,
they can hurt you really bad.
Listen, Dad,
I need to get something through to you.
I was hurting as a kid.
And the one person who caused
all that pain when I was younger,
the person who hurt me,
do you have any clue who that is?
Who is it?
Forget about it.
If you don't know, you never will.
They applied for it,
so we can get that done for them.
WELFARE COUNSELING
I don't have my ID,
but could I get a copy…
Maybe my Dad's onto something,
and the Vanguard can't be trusted.
What if all this is just a mind game?
That's my place.
ALCOHOLIC ATTORNEY
Should I ask Attorney Byeon?
Trust me, I know it's tough,
but only you can take them on.
No way. He'd chew me out
for even considering it.
What about Chairwoman Park?
Including the cost of the test,
it's 3 billion, 5 million won.
DEBT JEONG-JA
That's it.
Out of everyone in my life,
there's just one person left to ask.
Welcome. Come in.
Guess you started dinner.
Here. In case you're still hungry.
I heard they only bake 200 loaves a day.
I went to the mall
on my lunch break earlier
and waited forever in line to buy it.
You think I like bread?
Where'd you get that idea?
I just thought…
Forget it.
You can save them for later
if you need to fight anyone.
So I'm supposed to drag
this giant thing around?
Not the whole bag,
I had them wrapped individually
so you could…
Honestly, there's something
I'm curious about.
What's going on?
Uh, has anyone sold
superpowers for cash?
Who told you that?
Huh?
Come on, don't play stupid. Who told you?
The Vanguard.
That's what those bastards told me.
Everyone except us has sold.
What are you saying?
That our friend, Attorney Byeon…
he's known all along.
What are we doing here?
You said you were curious
about selling our superpowers.
Well, I just wanna know.
Is it even possible to sell them?
Is something like that dangerous?
I know for sure, powers can be extracted.
That guy had Hwa-jin's somehow.
Huh.
And who is she, Hwa-jin?
Are you selling or not?
Okay.
You're positive
the answers are in the safe?
Every cent counts.
BEOMHA GROUP
MISSING SUPERHUMANS LIST
SOLD FOR 400 MILLION WON
PERSUASION HIGHLY UNLIKELY
SUPERPOWER GENE
DISCOVERY AND INHERITANCE
SOLD FOR 70 MILLION
SOLD FOR 20 MILLION
SOLD FOR 30 MILLION WON
"Even if not bequeathed,
powers are inherited by children
after death."
Wait a minute.
Does that mean I'll pass it down
to my children, no matter what?
Yeah. Just like any inheritance.
It's a superpower, not a savings account.
LEE HWA-JIN
A SUDDEN BURST OF FIRE
AND EXPLOSIVE COMBAT POWER
SOLD FOR ABOUT 80 MILLION WON
I thought she was dead.
I wonder
how come none of them stayed in touch.
If I had just barely got out like her,
I wouldn't wanna talk either.
Shit.
KANG SANG-UNG, 35, CIVIL SERVANT
POWER: STRENGTH, HEALING
SON OF KANG DONG-GI
WORTH 1.3 BILLION WON
Low income paired with a desire
to move up in the world.
Prevent contact with the Vanguard
at all costs.
High likelihood of betrayal.
BYEON HO-IN
DIAGNOSIS: HEPATOCELLULAR CARCINOMA
You have to stop drinking immediately.
The chances for recovery are very low.
Have you informed your family
about the results?
Uh,
I haven't. Not yet.
You don't have much time left.
You should get your affairs in order.
BANG EUN-MI
With food…
you eventually eat your fill.
With drink, you eventually get drunk.
There are always limits
to everything.
All things, except for one.
Do you know what that is?
It's money.
No matter how much money you have,
you'll never have enough.
You reach for it,
but it's always beyond your grasp.
This world we've built
is overflowing with cash,
which means
his powers are potentially infinite,
and soon, he'll figure that out.
And so?
So, it's better to buy it now,
even if it costs billions to get it.
Look, Dad, I made a mistake.
But if you give me a few more days,
I'll be able--
I made a call to the US.
He'll be in town by next week.
I trust you can handle the final sale
by yourself?
Earn your meal at least.
Thanks for dinner.
Everyone's dealing with their own issues.
Everyone,
which explains why they do
whatever the hell they want.
My dad does it.
So does Attorney Byeon.
Bun-mi, Chairwoman Park,
even the Mundane Vanguard.
Have you made a decision?
I'm ready to sell.
How much would you like?
PRIVATE LOAN, MOM'S POOL, DEPOSIT
TOTAL
4,001,650,000 WON
If you're unsure,
I can give you an offer--
4,001,650,000.
Shit. Did I ask for too much?
-Done.
-I should've asked for more!
As soon as we've prepared everything,
I'll give you a time and place.
Ha!
Min-suk!
Min-suk! I did it!
Thank you.
Hey, Min-suk. I have a surprise.
-We just had dinner.
-Ta-da!
Hey. Don't be crazy.
Why would you buy this?
-Are you a millionaire all of a sudden?
-I know this ice cream is your favorite.
Every now and then,
you have to throw your money around.
-Here. Have some--
-Okay, but this…
This is the expensive brand!
What's going on?
So good. Oh my God, it's delicious.
You lost your mind.
Come on now, eat up.
We're going somewhere.
I'm so tired.
Where are we going?
So what's this surprise?
You've been acting weird all day.
What? Are you crazy?
Save it for our place, stud.
It's not what you think.
Just follow my lead.
-Hold on to me.
-Huh?
You know I'm by your side
When everybody turns their back to you
You know where to turn to
I won't ever let you down
-Take my hand
-Huh?
You and I together
-Through the fire
-I got you.
Through the thick and thin
We'll get over, you'll be fine
'Cause I'll always be here
You okay?
And if somebody ever lets you down
I'll run to you to calm you down
I swear, as long as I'm with you
You know you're safe and sound
Oh, oh, oh, oh…
-You see all those apartments?
-Hmm?
Those and the stars in the sky.
Know what they have in common?
I don't know. What?
I'm gonna get them all for you.
Sure you are.
How about we start
by getting you one of these stars?
I have a little spare cash.
From here to there would be…
-Let me see.
-Sang-ung.
-All right.
-Sang-ung, don't.
One.
Hang on. Sang-ung, this is crazy!
-You're just kidding, right?
-Get out of the blast zone. Two.
Sang-ung, it's too far!
You're gonna kill yourself!
Three!
I proposed without getting a ring.
I hope this one works.
Perfect.
Promise you like it?
-Wait.
-What's wrong?
There's something going on.
It's all right. You can tell me.
I feel like the hard times are over now.
This has all been a crazy adventure.
But it's time to face reality.
Hey.
You're making me nervous. What's going on?
I've decided to start over.
I'm right here.
Just tell me what's really going on.
Once things clear up,
I can tell you everything.
You think you can wait?
I'll let it slide today.
It's so pretty.
I guess that superpower
is not so useless after all.
You're right.
That was the first moment
of real peace I'd felt
since gaining my superpowers.
CHANGIL-DONG ADMINISTRATIVE WELFARE CENTER
Good morning, everybody.
-Thanks.
-Come on in.
Hi there. Good morning.
-Good morning.
-Good morning. Good to see you.
-Hello.
-Thanks.
-Hi, good morning.
Hello.
Hi, good morning.
Heavy, right?
I really appreciate it.
I see you're back to your old self.
I wanna start over.
I'll have a new attitude from now on.
The nice guy in the office
is officially back!
Hello.
I'm registering an address.
-Have you filled out the change request?
-Yeah.
Here you go.
All right.
I've never seen that name before.
It's really cool.
Jo Nathan's the name.
NAME: JO NATHAN
And may I have your previous address?
I just recently returned from the States.
Oh, of course. Right on.
Previous residence…
You know, I see all that you do.
Helping all those people,
always in secret.
That's the kind of hero
we need in the world.
Sorry?
The thing is,
I'm also working on a secret plan
that will change the world.
I signed up for the civil service.
Oh, you're a civil servant.
I thought you meant… Oh, man.
Hey, I wish you all the best.
I really appreciate it.
Mr. Kang.
Yeah?
Is everything okay?
There are police outside looking for you.
CHANGIL-DONG ADMINISTRATIVE WELFARE CENTER
-You two, cover the back!
-Yes, sir.
I haven't committed a crime.
Should I just walk out?
No.
What if that leads me
to getting arrested again?
I have to sell my superpower
no matter what.
Then they'll have nothing to pin on me.
Sorry. Can you finish
this customer's address change?
It turns out I'm urgently needed
outside the office.
-Hey, Mr. Kang.
-Bye.
Officer Hyeon-gi.
Kang Sang-ung. Is he around?
-Mr. Kang!
-Sh!
Oh no.
He's headed out the back!
Oh shit!
Hey, man! Are you okay?
-I need the truck!
-Where are you taking it?
Hey, hey!
BASTARD CHAIRMAN OF THE MUNDANE VANGUARD
Yes?
Hello, sir.
Sorry for calling out of nowhere,
but it's urgent.
Can I sell what we talked about now?
You mean today?
BEOMHA RANCH
What the hell is he doing?
Kang Sang-ung.
You came out of nowhere.
Shouldn't you be at work right now?
I'm working outside the office.
What about you, Attorney Byeon?
Shouldn't you
be at your office right now too?
It's being repaired.
It was damaged after somebody broke in.
Ah…
You holding any cash?
You bring any alcohol?
SOJU
I wonder what these guys are up to.
Just let me go.
-Please. I don't like hurting my friends.
-It's a betrayal to sell it.
Oh, yeah? According to who?
That's for me to decide.
Huh?
How could you do this to me?
You knew about this all along
and kept me in the dark.
It's not important to know everything.
Why not?
It can cause weakness.
And you decide what makes me weak?
BEOMHA RANCH
I like these.
I thought you would.
-Whoa!
-Oh, come on.
Knock it off!
He's not playing around.
This is too much.
Seriously?
Hey! Why are you attacking me?
Beomha Ranch? Why is he there?
We don't know.
Do not let him go in there.
Do whatever it takes!
JEONGJA LOANS
CHAIRWOMAN PARK JEONG-JA
Come on, enough.
Can't you see it's part of their plan
to make us fight each other?
You're the one who lied to us
about being able to sell our powers.
Remember?
Was that their plan too?
That was for your own good!
Will you just grow up already?!
Right.
You can't wait to give everyone a lecture
on the greater good,
but in the end,
you do exactly what you want,
just like every other boomer!
What? What?!
We've talked about
controlling that anger, Bun-mi.
Deep breaths.
You know why you hate
people selling their powers so much?
It's because you're jealous
no one tried to get yours!
Of course they did!
You're lying again.
Oh my God! You're lying again!
I can't trust a goddamn word you say!
That prick's going inside!
Go! Stop him!
Go, go!
Sang-ung, wait!
Oh. Is he okay?
Is he going in?
No way. He made it to the entry.
BEOMHA RANCH
Did you miss me?
First of all…
the money.
Ah, the money.
Of course.
The bag.
And I thought
you were one of the principled ones.
I should've known a few pennies
would bring you crawling back.
Count it if you want.
No, I think I'm good.
Have a seat.
BEOMHA
BIO LOGICS
-I can fly
-Fly
Supernatural
I got the power
Devils in the night
-Try to fight
-Fight
Nothing can be stopped
Follow you tonight
This is all my life
Power's mine
Give me all the cash
I feel the fire now
Try to punch you, smash
Devil is into your mind
I am cynical, but I feel powerful
I can crush you now
Time is done you better run
Let me whisper to your mind
You will feel the burn
Supernatural
I got the power on my mind
I can give you all the pain
Till the break of dawn
I can fly up the sky
Every day and night
Drop it on the floor
Better listen now
You got nothing
And I know that this is over now
Chasing you around
Round merry-go-round
Boo, I got you
You will never see the light
Let me whisper to your mind
You will feel the burn
Supernatural
I got the power on my mind
I can give you all the pain
Till the break of dawn
I can fly up the sky
Every day and night
Burn the lonely eyes
Crucify your lies
Now you cry
You better run
Run it speed of light
You better run, run it till you fight
Pain through your heart
Pain through your soul
It's time
-I can fly
-Fly
Supernatural
I got the power
Devils in the night
-Try to fight
-Fight
Nothing can be stopped
Follow you tonight
This is all my life
Power's mine
No one else can find you now
Only devils on your side
You will see the darkest night
-I can fly
-Fly
Supernatural
I got the power
Devils in the night
-Try to fight
-Fight
Nothing can be stopped
Follow you tonight
This is all my life
Power's mine